Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) National Office Records WAG.281
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Negotiations
  - Commercial Radio Code: NPR (Includes Agreements re: Actors' Equity), 1980-1984 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Commercial Radio Code: NPR Annual Report, 1983 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Commercial Radio Code: NPR Opera Agreement, 1977-1978 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - Commercial Radio Code: NPR Opera Agreement, 1980-1985 (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - Commercial Radio Code: NPR Project ONE and Earplay, 1975-1980 (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - Interim Agreements, 1988 (Box 128, Folder 17)
  - Music Video re: Rates and Conditions: Correspondence from British Equity, 1984 (Box 128, Folder 18)
  - National Negotiations: AFRA, 1943 (Box 128, Folder 19)
  - National Negotiations for 1952-1954: Notices, 1953 (Box 128, Folder 20)
  - National Negotiations for 1954-1956 (Box 128, Folder 21)
  - National Negotiations for 1956-1958, undated (Box 128, Folder 22)
  - National Negotiations for 1956-1958: Notices (Box 128, Folder 23)
  - National Negotiations for 1958-1960: Groot, Ken Worksheets, Reports and Memos, 1959 (Box 128, Folder 24)
  - National Negotiations for 1958-1960: Notices, 1958-1959 (Box 128, Folder 25)
  - National Negotiations for 1958-1960: Proposals, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1958-1959 (Box 128, Folder 26)
  - National Negotiations for 1960-1963: Chicago Local Proposals (Box 128, Folder 27)
  - National Negotiations for 1960-1963: Correspondence, Notes and Related Materials, Aug 1960 (Box 128, Folder 28)
  - National Negotiations for 1960-1963: Correspondence, Notes and Related Materials, Sept 1960 (Box 128, Folder 29)
  - National Negotiations for 1960-1963: Correspondence, Notes and Related Materials, Oct 1960-Dec 1960 (Box 128, Folder 30)
  - National Negotiations for 1960-1963: Industry Proposals, 1960-1961 (Box 128, Folder 31)
  - National Negotiations for 1960-1963: LA Local Proposals (Box 128, Folder 32)
  - National Negotiations for 1960-1963: NY Local Proposals and Caucus Meetings (Box 128, Folder 33)
  - National Negotiations for 1960-1963: Notices, 1960-1961 (Box 128, Folder 34)
  - National Negotiations for 1960-1963: Wages and Working Condition Committee (Box 128, Folder 35)
  - National Negotiations for 1963-1966: Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 128, Folder 36)
  - National Negotiations for 1963-1966: Chicago Local Recommendations (Box 128, Folder 37)
  - National Negotiations for 1963-1966: Dancers Recommendations (Box 128, Folder 38)
  - National Negotiations for 1963-1966: LA Local Recommendations (Box 128, Folder 39)
  - National Negotiations for 1963-1966: NY Local Recommendations (Box 128, Folder 40)
  - National Negotiations for 1963-1966: Newsmen and Staff Announcers, 1963-1964 (Box 128, Folder 41)
  - National Negotiations for 1963-1966: Notices, 1963-1964 (Box 128, Folder 42)
  - National Negotiations for 1963-1966: Strike Meetings (Box 128, Folder 43)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: ABC, etc. vs. AFTRA etc., et al., 1967 (Box 128, Folder 44)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Clippings, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 45)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Correspondence, Nov 1966-Mar 1967 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Correspondence, Apr 3-9, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Correspondence, Apr 10-30, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Correspondence, May 1967-Aug 1968 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Groot, Ken File, 1960-1967 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Huntley, Chet Correspondence and Related Materials, Mar 1967-Sep 1967 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Notices and Related Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Proposals, Mimeographed Version (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Proposals, Recommendations, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1966-1967 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike "AFRA Strike News" and Related Materials, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike: Assignments and Notices, Nov 1966 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike Expenses Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: "Strike History: Told in Chronology", 1967 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike Information compiled by Art Schroeder, Sr., Madison, Wisconsin Local, Nov 16, 1966-Apr 27, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike scrapbook, Nov 1966-Dec 1966 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike scrapbook, Jan 24, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike scrapbook, Mar 20-29, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike scrapbook, Mar 30, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike scrapbook, Mar 31, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 19)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike scrapbook, Apr 2-5, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 20)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike scrapbook, Apr 6-9, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 21)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike scrapbook, Apr 10-24, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 22)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike telegrams, Mar 1967 (Box 129, Folder 23)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike telegrams and related correspondence, Apr 1967 (Box 129, Folder 24)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike Two: NABET, correspondence and related materials, Sep 1967 (Box 129, Folder 25)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike Two: NABET, correspondence and related materials, Oct 1967-Dec 1967 (Box 129, Folder 26)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike Two: NABET disciplinary proceedings, 1968-1969 (Box 129, Folder 27)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike Two: NABET, scrapbook, ABC strike leading into official NABET strike, Jun 3, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 28)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike Two: NABET, scrapbook, Aug 1967 (Box 129, Folder 29)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike Two: NABET, scrapbook (specifically ABC), Sep 1967 (Box 129, Folder 30)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike Two: NABET, scrapbook, Oct 1967 (Box 129, Folder 31)
  - National Negotiations for 1966-1969: Strike Two: NABET, scrapbook, Nov 1967 (Box 129, Folder 32)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Attendance Records, 1969-1970 (Box 129, Folder 33)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Convention Resolutions (Box 129, Folder 34)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Correspondence and Related Materials, Feb 1969-Jan 1970 (Box 129, Folder 35)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Correspondence and Related Materials, Feb 1970-Aug 1970 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Materials from Binder (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Network Newsmen Statistics, Surveys and Ralted Materials, 1969-1970 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Notices (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Progress Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Proposals (final versions) (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Support by other Unions (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Wages and Working Conditions Committee (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Wolff, Sanford "Bud" Correspondence, Aug 1969-Mar 1970 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Wolff Correspondence, Apr 1970-Oct 1970 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - National Negotiations for 1969-1972: Wolff Correspondence Notes and Related Materials (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - National Negotiations for 1972-1974 (became 1973): Correspondence, Proposals and Related Materials, Oct 1971-Mar 1972 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - National Negotiations for 1972-1974 (became 1973): Correspondence, Proposals and Related Materials, Jun 1972-Nov 1972 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - National Negotiations for 1972-1974 (became 1973): Wolff Folder (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - National Negotiations for 1972-1974 (became 1973): Extension Letter (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - National Negotiations for 1976-1979: Wolff binder including Network TV and Newsmen, 1969-1975 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - National Negotiations for 1976-1979: Wolff binder including New York Local Agreements, 1969-1975 (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - National Negotiations for 1976-1979: Wolff binder including Proposals, 1969-1975 (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - National Negotiations for 1976-1979: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975-1977 (Box 130, Folder 19)
  - National Negotiations for 1979-1982: Correspondence, Proposals and Related Materials (Box 130, Folder 20)
  - National Negotiations for 1979-1982: Correspondence, Proposals and Related Materials, 1980-1981 (Box 130, Folder 21)
  - National Negotiations for 1982-1985, 1982-1983 (Box 130, Folder 22)
  - National Negotiations for 1982-1985: Attendance Sheets, 1982-1983 (Box 130, Folder 23)
  - National Negotiations for 1982-1985: SAG Materials, 1982-1983 (Box 130, Folder 24)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Correspondence and Related Materials (Box 130, Folder 25)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: General Session Minutes, May 27, 1986-Jun 23, 1986 (Box 130, Folder 26)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: General Session Minutes, Jun 24, 1986-Jun 29, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Hall Binder, Background Information Including 1982-1985 Network TV Code, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Hall Binder, Background Information Including Prime Time TV, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Hall Binder, Background Information Including Producer/SAG Agreement of 1977, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Hall Binder, Background Information Including SAG Agreement of 1977 and 1980, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Hall Binder Part I, Salary and Schedules, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Hall Binder Part II, General Provisions, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Hall Binder Parts III-IV, Employment of Minors, Singers, Dancers, Stunts, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Hall Binder Parts VII-VIII, Pay TV and Parity, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Hall Binder Part IX, Clarification and Additional Uncatalogued Materials, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Walker, Terry Binder, P&W Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Walker, Terry Binder, Primarily Radio, 1986-1987 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - National Negotiations for 1985-1988: Walker, Terry Binder, Primarily Television, 1986-1987 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - National Negotiations for 1988-1991: Caucus Notes, 1987-1988 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - National Negotiations for 1988-1991: Foreign Distribution (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - National Negotiations for 1988-1991: Singer Rates (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Network Staff Newsmen: National News Department Formation and Implementation, 1983-1985 (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Network Staff Newsmen for 1963-1966 (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Network Staff Newsmen for 1966-1969: Lists, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1966-1968 (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Network Staff Newsmen for 1969-1972, 1968-1970 (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1973-1976: CBS, 1975 (Box 131, Folder 21)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1973-1976: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975 (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1973-1976: NBC, 1975 (Box 131, Folder 23)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1976-1979: Agreement, Proposals and Related Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 131, Folder 24)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1976-1979: ABC, 1977-1978 (Box 131, Folder 25)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1976-1979: CBS, 1976-1978 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1976-1979: NBC, 1977-1978 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1979-1982: NBC, 1978 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1979-1982, 1979-1980 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1982-1985: ABC, 1982-1984 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1982-1985: CBS, 1981-1982 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1982-1985: Handwritten Notes, All Networks, undated (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1982-1985: NBC, 1983-1984 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: ABC, 1985-1986 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: Attendance Sheets, 1985-1986 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: CBS, 1985-1986 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: Final Proposal, 1986 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: Memoranda and Related Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: Memoranda and Related Materials, Feb 1986-Jul 1986 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: Memoranda and Related Materials, Aug 1986-Nov 1986 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: NBC, 1984-1986 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: NBC C-Day Reports A-K, 1986 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: NBC C-Day Reports L-W, 1986 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: "Newsmen Project" Earnings Statements, 1986 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: Pension and Welfare, All Networks, 1985-1986 (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: P&W Claims, 1984-1987 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: Walker, Terry Notes, 1985-1986 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988 and 1988-1991: Weber Lipshie Audit, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986-1991 (Box 132, Folder 23)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1985-1988: Wolff, "Bud" Notes (Box 132, Folder 24)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1988-1991: ABC Draft (Box 132, Folder 25)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1988-1991: CNN, 1987, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 26)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1988-1991: CBS Draft (Box 132, Folder 27)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1988-1991: Handwritten Notes and Related Materials, All Networks, 1987-1988 (Box 132, Folder 28)
  - Network Staff Newspersons for 1988-1991: NBC Draft (Box 132, Folder 29)
  - Non-Broadcast/Industrial/Educational Recorded Material for 1978-1982 (Box 132, Folder 30)
  - Non-Broadcast/Industrial/Educational for 1978-1982, 1979 (Box 132, Folder 31)
  - Non-Broadcast/Industrial/Educational for 1982-1985, 1982-1984 (Box 132, Folder 32)
  - Non-Broadcast/Industrial/Educational Recorded Material for 1985-1988, 1985-1986 (Box 132, Folder 33)
  - Non-Broadcast/Industrial/Educational Recorded Material for 1988-1990, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Non-Broadcast/Industrial/Educational Recorded Material for 1988-1990, 1988-1989 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Non-Broadcast/Industrial/Educational Recorded Material for 1990-1993 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Non-Broadcast/Industrial Contracts: Self-signatories, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Off-Air Videotaping for Educational Uses: Correspondence, Minutes and Related Materials, 1979 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Off-Air Videotaping for Educational Purposes: Correspondence, Minutes and Related Materials, 1980 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Off-Air Videotaping for Educational Purposes: Correspondence, Minutes and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Phonograph Recordings [Phono Code] for 1962-1965, Jun 1959-Dec 1961 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Phono Code for 1962-1965, Jan 1962-Mar 1962 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Phono Code for 1962-1965, Apr 1962-Aug 1962 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Phono Code for 1962-1965 (Donald Conaways Paper and Notes) (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Phono Code for 1962-1965: Signatories, 1961 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Phono Code for 1968-1971, Oct 1967-Dec 1967 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Phono Code for 1968-1971, Jan 1968-Feb 1968 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Phono Code for 1968-1971, Mar 1968 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Phono Code for 1968-1971, Apr 1968 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Phono Code for 1968-1971, May 1968-Dec 1968 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - Phono Code for 1968-1971: Signatories (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - Phono Code: Breakdowns, 1969-1970 (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - Phono Code: Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - Phono Code: Correspondence to/from Louis Nunley, 1969-1971 (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - Phono Code: Earnings, Capital Records, 1970-1972 (Box 133, Folder 22)
  - Phono Code: Earnings, Columbia Records, 1970-1972 (Box 133, Folder 23)
  - Phono Code: Earnings, RCA Records, 1970-1972 (Box 133, Folder 24)
  - Phono Code: Session Summaries from New York, Los Angeles and Chicago, 1969-1970 (Box 133, Folder 25)
  - Phono Code for 1971-1974: Attendance Records (Box 133, Folder 26)
  - Phono Code for 1971-1974: Convention Proposals and Related Materials, 1970 (Box 133, Folder 27)
  - Phono Code for 1971-1974: Correspondence (Box 133, Folder 28)
  - Phono Code for 1971-1974: Draft #2 of Proof (Box 133, Folder 29)
  - Phono Code for 1971-1974: Proposals and Related Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 133, Folder 30)
  - Phono Code for 1971-1974: Signatories for 1968-1971, Apr 30, 1970 (Box 133, Folder 31)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1979: Attendance Lists (Box 133, Folder 32)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1979: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 133, Folder 33)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1979: Drafts, 1974-1975 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1977: Kocin, Harold's Materials (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1977: Non-signatory and Non-member Project, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1977: Proof Copy, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1979: Proposals (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1977: Summary Sheets, 1973-1974 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1977: Wolff, Sanford "Bud's" Materials (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Phono Code for 1977-1980: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Phono Code for 1977-1980: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Phono Code for 1977-1980: NARM (National Association of Recording Merchandisers) Studies, 1973, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Phono Code for 1977-1980: Proof (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Phono Code for 1977-1980: Proposals, 1976-1977 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Phono Code for 1977-1980: Video Dish Supplement, 1979-1980 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Phono Code for 1977-1980: Singers Committee Minutes and Related Materials, 1975-1977 (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - Phono Code for 1977-1980: Summary Sheets (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Phono Code for 1980-1983: Draft, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Phono Code for 1980-1983: Proposals and Related Material, 1980-1982 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Phono Code for 1980-1983: A Perspective, 1981 (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - Phono Code for 1980-1983: Video Disc Supplement, 1979-1982 (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - Phono Code for 1983-1986: Proposals and Related Materials Including Video Promo, Feb 1983-Mar 1983 (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - Phono Code for 1983-1986: Proposals and Related Materials Including Video Promo, Apr 1983-Nov 1983 (Box 134, Folder 21)
  - Phono Code for 1987-1990: Correspondence, Proposals and Related Material, 1985-1986 (Box 134, Folder 22)
  - Phono Code for 1987-1990: Correspondence, Proposals and Related Material, 1987-1989 (Box 134, Folder 23)
  - Phono Code for 1990-1993: Correspondence, Drafts and Related Material, 1989-1990 (Box 134, Folder 24)
  - Phono Code for 1990-1993: Correspondence, Drafts and Related Material, 1991 (Box 134, Folder 25)
  - Phono Code: Audits, 1985-1989 (Box 134, Folder 26)
  - Phono Code: Performance Rights in Sound Recording Volume I, 1978 (Box 134, Folder 27)
  - Phono Code: Performance Rights in Sound Recording (from Volume I but not in bound copy)- Economic Impact Analysis of Proposed Change in Copyright Law, 1978 (Box 134, Folder 28)
  - Phono Code: Performance Rights in Sound Recording Volume II, 1978 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Policing of National Codes: Convention Resolution, Correspondence and Related Material, 1969-1972 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Public Telecommunications: Temporary Commission on Alternative Financing, 1981 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Radio Code for 1956-1958 and earlier, 1952, 1957 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Radio Code for 1958-1960, 1957-1959 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Radio Code: Program Schedules, 1969 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Radio Code for 1972-1974 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Radio Code for 1976-1979: Correspondence Notes and Related Material, 1977-1978 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Radio Code for 1979-1982 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Radio Code: National Public Radio Agreement for 1988-1990, 1989-1991 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials: Assumption Letters, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials: Assumption Letters, 1977-1979 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1979-1982: Correspondence, Proposal and Related Material (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1982-1985: Correspondence, Proposal and Related Material (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1982-1985: Gallyes (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1982-1985: Proofs (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1985-1988: Correspondence and Related Material, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1985-1988: Correspondence and Related Material (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1985-1988: Signatories, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1988-1991, 1989 (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - Side Letters (Various Codes), 1964 (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - Signatories: Code Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - Signatory Lists, Dec 1984-Dec 1985 (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - Signatory Lists, Jan 1986-May 1986 (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - Signatory Lists, Jun 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 135, Folder 25)
  - Signatory Lists, Jan 1987-May 1987 (Box 135, Folder 26)
  - Signatory Lists, Jun 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 135, Folder 27)
  - Slide Film Recordings for 1966-1969: Signatories (Box 135, Folder 28)
  - Slide Film Recordings for 1969-1972: Signatories, 1971 (Box 135, Folder 29)
  - Slide Film Recordings for 1972-1974: Proposals, Correspondence and Related Material (Box 135, Folder 30)
  - Slide Film Recordings [Non-Broadcast Recorded Material], 1973 (Box 135, Folder 31)
  - Slide Film Recordings [Non-Broadcast Recorded Material], 1974 (Box 135, Folder 32)
  - Slide Film Recordings [Non-Broadcast Recorded Material], 1975 (Box 135, Folder 33)
  - Slide Film Recordings [Non-Broadcast Recorded Material], 1976-1977 (Box 135, Folder 34)
  - Staff Announcers for 1956-1958, 1957 (Box 135, Folder 35)
  - Staff Announcers for 1958-1960: Proposals, Correspondence and Related Material, 1958-1959 (Box 135, Folder 36)
  - Staff Announcers for 1960-1963: ABC (Box 135, Folder 37)
  - Staff Announcers for 1960-1963: CBS, 1960-1961 (Box 135, Folder 38)
  - Staff Announcers for 1960-1963: NBC, 1960-1961 (Box 135, Folder 39)
  - Staff Announcers for 1960-1963: Proposals and Related Material (Box 135, Folder 40)
  - Staff Announcers for 1963-1966, 1963-1964 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Staff Announcers for 1966-1969: CBS New York (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Staff Announcers for 1966-1969: NBC New York (Box 136, Folder 3)